this tutorial is about V vaults one of
本教程是有关V Vault的
弹出窗口中最重要的机制
this tutorial is about V vaults one of
the most important mechanisms in pop-up
设计，所以我将从谈起
关于我们将要使用的材料
the most important mechanisms in pop-up
design and so I'll just start by talking
在本教程中使用，所以大多数
重要的是这是160 GSM卡
design and so I'll just start by talking
about the materials that we're going to
影印卡，您可以使用更重的
卡，甚至可以使用沉重的
about the materials that we're going to
be using in this tutorial so most
在这种情况下，墨盒纸为160 GSM
其他材料很粘
be using in this tutorial so most
important is the card this is 160 GSM
重要的是最好的胶水是溶剂型
水性粘合剂会起作用，并且
important is the card this is 160 GSM
photocopy card and you can use heavier
水基的问题会上升吗
速度较慢，因此很难使用
photocopy card and you can use heavier
cards or you can even use heavy
而且它也倾向于扣卡
你不会得到如此令人满意的结果
cards or you can even use heavy
cartridge paper in this case is 160 GSM
你也可以用胶水粘
胶水非常干净非常快速非常容易
cartridge paper in this case is 160 GSM
the other materials is glue very
为了制作粗糙的假人
绝对可以，但如果您弹出
the other materials is glue very
important the best glue is solvent based
你想持续很重要
给你粘胶往往会干裂
important the best glue is solvent based
adhesive water-based will work and the
然后你的弹出窗口会崩溃
您需要的另一件事是
adhesive water-based will work and the
problem with water based is it goes up
剪刀，任何剪刀都会做卡胶
剪刀就是您所需要的
problem with water based is it goes up
more slowly so it's harder to work with
教程以及大多数其他教程
弹出窗口需要一个基础，因此我们从
more slowly so it's harder to work with
and it also tends to buckle the card so
只是将一张卡片对折
真的把它弄得很彻底
and it also tends to buckle the card so
you don't get so such pleasing results
过分强调对
折起卡片，然后将其折回
you don't get so such pleasing results
you can also use stick glue and stick
本身
再折一次，这是你的基础
you can also use stick glue and stick
glue is very clean very quick very easy
有三个原则
波普尔的第一个原则是
glue is very clean very quick very easy
and for making rough dummies it's
弹出窗口必须跨越一个沟渠，第一个
沟是脊椎向下折
and for making rough dummies it's
absolutely fine but if you make a pop-up
第二个原则是
每个弹出窗口都必须跨越一个沟壑
absolutely fine but if you make a pop-up
that you want to last that's important
必须固定在每一侧，
必须在
that you want to last that's important
to you stick glue tends to dry out crack
沟渠，所以这里是沟渠
V形褶皱就是我们在说的
to you stick glue tends to dry out crack
and then your pop ups will fall apart
关于本教程中的角度
平衡，所以在弹出的角度
and then your pop ups will fall apart
the other thing you need is a pair of
双方都是相同的
每边的角度是
the other thing you need is a pair of
scissors any scissors will do card glue
同样的第三条原则是
弹出窗口会创建沟壑，所以在这里我们有一个
scissors any scissors will do card glue
scissors that's all you need in this
弹出这是在
中间，这是一个平行四边形卡住
scissors that's all you need in this
tutorial and most of the others so all
进入它的弹出式窗口
基本的沟口提高
tutorial and most of the others so all
pop ups need a base and so we start by
弹出，然后弹出Scully
打开会弹出其中的弹出窗口，
pop ups need a base and so we start by
just folding a sheet of card in half
这是另一个例子，这又是
这是另一个V形折叠，但在这种情况下
just folding a sheet of card in half
crease it really thoroughly I can't
底孔打开沟壑凸起
弹出粉红色的位，这些
crease it really thoroughly I can't
overemphasize how important it is to to
两个平行四边形卡在
父亲创造的沟渠，所以
overemphasize how important it is to to
crease the card so fold it fold it back
每个弹出群众的三个原则
Panigale每个弹出窗口必须保持平衡
crease the card so fold it fold it back
on itself
在沟渠的每一侧，每个弹出窗口
创造出更多动力的沟壑
on itself
crease it again this is your base
可以卡住，所以这是三个
原理，所以现在我们继续
there is there are three principles in
实际v折
有五种V型折叠
there is there are three principles in
popper the first principle is that every
第一个是直角
V形折叠，因此弹出窗口上的角度为
popper the first principle is that every
pop-up must span a gully and the first
都是90度，所以这是第一个
这是第二个，这是急性的
pop-up must span a gully and the first
gully is the spine fold down the middle
v角折叠，因此每一侧的角度
的沟渠都小于90度
gully is the spine fold down the middle
of the base the second principle is that
这是v型折叠的第二种类型
第三，这是尖锐的V型折叠
of the base the second principle is that
every pop-up must span a gully so it
锐角v折的变化
真的，但是顶端而不是顶端
every pop-up must span a gully so it
must be stuck down on each side and it
站着自豪，这归结为打击
这是v型折叠的第三种类型的页面
must be stuck down on each side and it
must be balanced on each side of the
再次在每一侧的角度
中央折痕相同
must be balanced on each side of the
gully so here's the gully in this case
折叠的类型
这是默认的钝角
gully so here's the gully in this case
with v-folds which is what we're talking
这一个在弹出的角度
中央折痕的每一边
with v-folds which is what we're talking
about in this tutorial it's the angles
两者都超过90度
事情希腊默认，最后我们有
about in this tutorial it's the angles
that balance so on the pop-up the angles
不对称的v-fold
所以这个不对称的v-fold
that balance so on the pop-up the angles
on each side are the same and on the
所有四个角度都不相同
弹出窗口上的角度不同
on each side are the same and on the
base the angles on each side are the
底座上的两个角度不同，但
仍然在左边的角度
base the angles on each side are the
same the third principle is that every
弹出框加上底边等于角度
在弹出窗口和底座的右侧
same the third principle is that every
pop-up creates gullies so here we have a
所以我们又有了平衡
这是五折的五种类型
pop-up creates gullies so here we have a
pop-up this is a gully created in the
在本教程中，我们只是与
这两个直角v-折和
pop-up this is a gully created in the
middle and here's a parallelogram stuck
锐角v形折叠，所以我把这些
其他人走了以后
middle and here's a parallelogram stuck
into it so it's the pop-up rising the
教程
因此，我们首先制作一个
into it so it's the pop-up rising the
gully the basic gully opening raises the
直角v形折叠，所以我们取一个底
折页完全折痕，然后
gully the basic gully opening raises the
pop-up and then the pop-up Scully
我们再拿一张纸牌
制作实际的弹出窗口，让我们尝试一下粉红色
pop-up and then the pop-up Scully
opening raises the pop-up within it and
一块只是把它切成两半
眼睛其实并不重要
opening raises the pop-up within it and
here's another example this is again
将其折成两半
折回去，所以我不能
here's another example this is again
it's another v-fold but in this case the
过分强调它对
彻底折起所有褶皱
it's another v-fold but in this case the
the base opening opens the gully raises
起伏，然后我们想要每个角度
这边这将是你的
the base opening opens the gully raises
the pop-up the pink bit and that these
弹出窗口像这样在您的
页面，因此我们需要每个角度
the pop-up the pink bit and that these
two parallelograms are stuck into the
边相等，所以在这种情况下我们折叠
它关闭并折叠一些折痕到
two parallelograms are stuck into the
gullies created by the father so the
底部再折好
那你就必须切掉角落
gullies created by the father so the
three principles every pop-up mass
所以从那一点开始
收敛，你只是切出那个角度，
three principles every pop-up mass
Panigale every pop-up must be balanced
剪掉那一点，所以你有了这些
现在将这种形状粘在标签上
Panigale every pop-up must be balanced
on each side of the gully every pop-up
你把那块切下来就可以折叠
这些都单独回来并弄皱
on each side of the gully every pop-up
creates gullies which more power works
真的很彻底，就是那个
这个还可以，所以我们弹出了
creates gullies which more power works
can be stuck into so those are the three
件和每个侧面的角度是
匹配，所以我们知道我们有平衡
can be stuck into so those are the three
principles so now we move on to the
现在我们需要坚持下去
这些V形折叠部分的分页方式
principles so now we move on to the
actual v-fold
向下，它们朝着
V指向，所以这个要走
there are five kinds of v-folds this is
以这种方式折叠下来，所以它需要
靠近你的前面
there are five kinds of v-folds this is
the first one this is the right angle
页面，然后贴上角度
它对基地它可以是任何东西
the first one this is the right angle
v-fold so the angles on the pop-up are
你喜欢你可以有这样的形状
真的紧紧地靠在一起
v-fold so the angles on the pop-up are
both 90 degrees so that's the first one
或者您可以将它打开得更广泛
可以像你想的那样宽
both 90 degrees so that's the first one
this is the second one this is the acute
与脊柱成90度（如果是90度）
度到
this is the second one this is the acute
angle v-fold so the angles on each side
买整个东西会跌倒
向下，所以它必须小于90
angle v-fold so the angles on each side
of the gully both less than 90 degrees
在中央沟和它的位置之间
粘合到页面和粘合方式
of the gully both less than 90 degrees
that's the the second type of v-fold the
这些只是通过粘贴一个标签开始，所以我们
在上面放一点胶
that's the the second type of v-fold the
third this is the pointy v-fold so it's
把它涂在右边
我用我的小手指的错，是
third this is the pointy v-fold so it's
a variation on the acute angle v-fold
不要让胶水粘在我的另一只手上
其他手指，所以我仍然可以使用所有
a variation on the acute angle v-fold
really but the the top rather than
其他手指也使东西排列整齐
弹出窗口的中央沟
really but the the top rather than
standing proud it comes down to to hit
基部中央沟的那一点
放下并使其变得有趣
standing proud it comes down to to hit
the page that's the third type of v-fold
你把胶水涂在另一个标签上
直到折痕边缘不是真的
the page that's the third type of v-fold
again the angles on each side of the
重要的是总是弹出
减少您需要涂抹胶水
again the angles on each side of the
central crease are the same the fourth
对折痕进行任何测量
总是将折痕折叠起来并关闭
central crease are the same the fourth
type of v-fold
这是直角V型折叠
V折的直角V折是
type of v-fold
this is the obtuse angle default so in
对建筑学科真的很好
所以这是我做的一个
this is the obtuse angle default so in
this one the angles on the pop up on
是一个这是直角V折
养一个花园
this one the angles on the pop up on
each side of the central crease they're
平行四边形，所以这是第一个
平行四边形，它粘在这个沟渠中
each side of the central crease they're
both more than 90 degrees that's the two
的V折，这就是
第二个平行四边形粘贴到此
both more than 90 degrees that's the two
things Greek default and finally we have
沟渠
所以当页面关闭整个
things Greek default and finally we have
the asymmetric v-fold
配置上升并掉落
这本书罗恩的奇幻童话
the asymmetric v-fold
so is the asymmetric v-fold in this one
范德米尔
都是用这种直角制成的
so is the asymmetric v-fold in this one
all four angles are different the two
V折，所以如果我们略过
第一个是V倍加注
all four angles are different the two
angles on the pop-up are different the
这个平行四边形的房子到下一个
页面，在这种情况下是V形折叠
angles on the pop-up are different the
two angles on the base are different but
更开放
比以前的一遍又一遍
two angles on the base are different but
still the angles on the left on the
在这里有一个平行四边形
平行四边形在这里粘到这个
still the angles on the left on the
pop-up plus the base equals the angles
V型折页粘在页面上的沟
这是第三个，这是一个
pop-up plus the base equals the angles
on the right on the pop-up and the base
直角V折和这张小桌子
这是直角V折
on the right on the pop-up and the base
so again we've got we've got balance so
在这里提高平行四边形作为页面
关闭，您可以看到主要的是
so again we've got we've got balance so
those are the five types of v-fold
朝着
V指向和桌子
those are the five types of v-fold
in this tutorial we're just working with
朝着方向折叠
这些指向，所以他们都折叠起来
in this tutorial we're just working with
these two the right angle v-folds and
彼此，这是最终的
一
these two the right angle v-folds and
the acute angle v-fold so i put these
这是一个很大的大直角V折
与平行四边形数组这是
the acute angle v-fold so i put these
other ones away they come up in a later
第一个粘在这个沟里
这是内置于此的第二个
other ones away they come up in a later
tutorial
居利这是内置的第三个
页面关闭整个过程
so we start by making one we'll make a
当你看着整个回转
弹出窗口不是绝对平坦的
so we start by making one we'll make a
right-angle v-folds so we take a base
倾向于成一个小角度，所以当
你看着这个直角V折
right-angle v-folds so we take a base
sheet folded thoroughly creased and then
这样，页面不是
完全平坦的外观无关紧要
sheet folded thoroughly creased and then
we'll take another sheet of cards to
但是如果你换个角度看
周围，​​所以你正在寻找
we'll take another sheet of cards to
make the actual pop-up let's try a pink
如果页面不在页面上
整个东西绝对平坦
make the actual pop-up let's try a pink
piece here just just cut it in half by
对你，所以这可能是你
想要是您设计的一部分，但
piece here just just cut it in half by
eye doesn't really doesn't really matter
否则你治愈的方式就是你
移动到锐角V折
fold it in half crease it thoroughly
这是一个锐角V折
山折指向你
fold it in half crease it thoroughly
fold it back on it so I can't
基地不一定要完全
平，但它仍然站立
fold it back on it so I can't
overemphasize how important it is to
直立起来，这种类型也很好
如果您以正确的角度V使用它
overemphasize how important it is to
thoroughly crease all the folds on pop
折叠，因为它靠近
您没有太多空间的页面
thoroughly crease all the folds on pop
ups and then we want the angles on each
插图文字或您想要的任何内容
而这种类型的锐角V折
ups and then we want the angles on each
side this is this is going to be your
因为V向你下方折
可以将整个东西放在
side this is this is going to be your
pop-up standing up like this on your
页面的背面，然后
您在基地上知道的足够空间
pop-up standing up like this on your
page and so we need the angles on each
有关更多插图，更多弹出文本
随你喜欢
page and so we need the angles on each
side to be equal so in this case we fold
所以你只看这本书
这是提防狼的故事书
side to be equal so in this case we fold
it shut and fold some creases onto the
纸工程是由M Corrine设计的
弗莱彻可爱的书，这是童话
it shut and fold some creases onto the
bottom and again crease them well and
用v形折叠制成的童话
实际上是不对称的V形折叠
bottom and again crease them well and
then you have to cut out the the corner
指向页面，以便您打开
仙女从书中掉出来的那一页
then you have to cut out the the corner
so from that point where the the creases
当您关闭页面时，它们非常
你知道跳回书中
so from that point where the the creases
converge you just cut out that angle and
这是一个非常令人愉快的使用
您知道的那种设计以及
converge you just cut out that angle and
and cut off that bit so you've got these
v形折叠在
指向的方式，所以现在我向您展示
and cut off that bit so you've got these
gluing tabs this shape and now now
如何使锐角v形折叠
你得到你的基础表并折叠它
gluing tabs this shape and now now
you've cut that piece out you can fold
将其折半
一次又一次在这里
you've cut that piece out you can fold
these back individually and crease them
我们将使我们的作品
将其折叠起来
these back individually and crease them
really thoroughly so that's that one and
将其折好一半然后
而以直角V折，我们
really thoroughly so that's that one and
this one okay so we've got our pop-up
刚从
在这种情况下的底部边缘
this one okay so we've got our pop-up
piece and the angles each side that are
把它折成一个角度
距底部约半英寸
piece and the angles each side that are
matching so we know we've got balance
角落，这是折叠的一面
向上倾斜，并且您折叠的角度是
matching so we know we've got balance
there now we need to stick it to the
这将决定
弹出您将其折叠的信息
there now we need to stick it to the
page the way part these V folds fold
当您打开它时，回到自己
折痕应该给你下降
page the way part these V folds fold
down they fold down in the direction at
指向箭头真的很重要
如果箭头指向下方，则如果
down they fold down in the direction at
the V is pointing so this one is going
箭头指向较少的钝角
不管怎样，v-fold我们都会把它们切开
the V is pointing so this one is going
to fold down this way so it needs to be
自下而上
对，这就是你
to fold down this way so it needs to be
near the front of your front of your
弹出窗口将像这样站立
在页面上查看情况如何
near the front of your front of your
page and then the angle that you stick
页面上的选项卡是否
实际上会重叠，就像
page and then the angle that you stick
it to the to the base it can be anything
这样会很紧
重叠，所以只修剪一点
it to the to the base it can be anything
you like you can have a shape like this
因此，您可以决定如何
关闭您想要的标签
you like you can have a shape like this
where it's really tight close together
他们都坚持脊柱
保持相同的距离
where it's really tight close together
or you can open it up wide and wider you
脊椎，但或者越宽
弹出窗口越躺下
or you can open it up wide and wider you
can go as wide as you like it mustn't be
然后你越紧
角度越多，弹出窗口将越容易站立
can go as wide as you like it mustn't be
at 90 degrees to the spine if it's 90
所以再次确保这些
页面上的角度匹配我们从
at 90 degrees to the spine if it's 90
degrees to the
粘合一侧，使它发光
在页面顶部附近，这样您就可以坚持
degrees to the
buying the whole thing can just fall
向下一侧确保中央
折痕与
buying the whole thing can just fall
down so it's got to be less than 90
基地，所以在这里它折叠成它
关闭位置，将胶水粘在另一个
down so it's got to be less than 90
between the central gully and where it's
其他选项卡使这里一团糟
然后关闭这个地方
between the central gully and where it's
gluing to the page and the way you glue
有锐角v-fold，所以
这些要理解的东西
gluing to the page and the way you glue
these just start by gluing one tab so we
如果想让V型折叠
站起来更多，要么摆角度
these just start by gluing one tab so we
put put a bit of glue on it
在较小的底座上，或者您将
如果你在锅上的角度更大
put put a bit of glue on it
smear it right to the right to the to
希望它躺下更多
底座上的角度更大，或者您
smear it right to the right to the to
the fault I use my little finger so it's
使弹出窗口上的角度更小
那真的是关键，所以
the fault I use my little finger so it's
not to get glue glue on my other hand
现在我们只看几个例子
这些如何使用这些弹出式窗口
not to get glue glue on my other hand
other fingers so I can still use all the
这是一个这是红色的一点
红色部分是锐角v形折叠，
other fingers so I can still use all the
other fingers too to make things line up
它有几个标签切入
顶部，这正在提高
other fingers too to make things line up
the central gully of the pop-up with the
这个蓝鸟，所以整个事情
合上时向前折叠
the central gully of the pop-up with the
central gully of the base stick that bit
这是另一个例子，这是
锐角v折
central gully of the base stick that bit
down and just make it make it fun now
提出一个数字，我们有几个
内置到计数器错误
down and just make it make it fun now
you put glue on the other tab smear this
沟壑，它在哪里连接页面
这些是什么引起了
you put glue on the other tab smear this
up to the crease the edges aren't really
武器，我们只看一下
几本书，所以这两个
up to the crease the edges aren't really
important in pop up this always
是中士的费用，如果
你看这是V形褶皱
important in pop up this always
decreases you need to smear the glue
在这里，您可以看到V型折叠
也许在侧面看
decreases you need to smear the glue
right up to the crease any measuring you
你可以看到有一对V形折叠
他们实际上正在筹集一个整体
right up to the crease any measuring you
do always to the crease fold it shut and
一系列平行四边形和V
沿方向折叠
do always to the crease fold it shut and
here is the right angle V fold this type
指向V形折叠朝上
页面，当您打开它时，它很漂亮
here is the right angle V fold this type
of V fold the right angle V fold is
制作所有数字的好方法
下来，所以这是一些v形折叠
of V fold the right angle V fold is
really good for architectural subjects
提高平行四边形是另一种
这里的例子是王牌飞机
really good for architectural subjects
so here's one this is one I've made this
我认为是Keith Mosely设计的
这是这是这是V
so here's one this is one I've made this
is a this is a right angle V fold
折叠并
它正在举起这架中心飞机
is a this is a right angle V fold
raising a garden it's raising
飞机是完全由
平行四边形，所以这是
raising a garden it's raising
parallelograms so this is the first
V形折叠这是厨房
平行四边形内置于该沟渠中
parallelograms so this is the first
parallelogram it's glued into this gully
是整个平行四边形阵列
像在
parallelogram it's glued into this gully
of the V fold and then this is the
页面打开，大量的设计
一个，最后有一对
of the V fold and then this is the
second parallelogram glued into this
这里有一些怪物岛
我认为是从1979年还是1980年
second parallelogram glued into this
gully
真正的第二波
弹出书，所以这是一本
gully
so as the page closes the whole
这是基于正确的价差
角度v形折叠，您有几个
so as the page closes the whole
configuration lifts up and falls away
柜台在这里折叠在顶部，所以这
整个过程可能就像那样
configuration lifts up and falls away
this book fantastic fairytales by Ron
将这些额外的折痕放入其中
下来给你这额外的一点
this book fantastic fairytales by Ron
van der Meer
尺寸是直角的
然后在下一页上
van der Meer
is all made of this type of right angle
锐角默认给你这个
怪物以及这些武器的工作方式
is all made of this type of right angle
V fold so if we just skim through it is
这与插槽有关
在成人另一个教程
V fold so if we just skim through it is
the first one this is the V fold raising
终于有一本书叫
弹出填充弹出填充和第一个
the first one this is the V fold raising
this parallelogram house to the next
传播其中有很多
仅有一侧的非常微小的V形折叠
this parallelogram house to the next
page this is the V fold in this case
计划给这些这些一些
树顶，所以你要关闭
page this is the V fold in this case
it's more open
是的，你可以继续下去，树木转向
进入并开始被替换
it's more open
than the previous one and again you've
机器，它们仍然是默认值
建筑物是平行四边形
than the previous one and again you've
got a parallelogram here and you've got
另一个教程就是这样
教程
got a parallelogram here and you've got
parallelograms here glued into this
我所说的一切都在这
本书弹出式设计和论文
parallelograms here glued into this
gully where the v-fold glues to the page
机械师和我所说的一切
关于今天的事在这本书中
gully where the v-fold glues to the page
this is the third one again this is a
您